Guide to the Howard Seifert Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- General Files, Part 1
  - Curriculum - Propulsion 1959-60 Plans (STL-UCLA (Box 11A, Folder 61)
  - Curriculum - Memo Re: Seminar on Electric Propulsion - AA 298, March 21, 1961 (Box 11A, Folder 62)
  - Curriculum - 280A Laboratory (possible) (Box 11A, Folder 63)
  - Curriculum - Curriculum Committee -, 1961 (Box 11A, Folder 64)
  - Curriculum - History Astro to 1962 (Box 11A, Folder 65)
  - Advisees (Box 11A, Folder 66)
  - Ignorance Explosion (Box 11A, Folder 67)
  - Freshman Seminar Topic, Must Science be Obscure?, November 2, 1970 (Box 11A, Folder 68)
  - Rambo 1970 Conference Cassandra Talk (Box 11A, Folder 69)
  - SDS Info - Student Revolt, 1969 (Box 11A, Folder 70)
  - Stamp Out Engineering Schools - Robert Hutchins, 1968 (Box 11A, Folder 71)
  - Packer, 1968 (Box 11A, Folder 72)
  - The Reluctant Astronaut S. Ramu and P. Johnson, March 20, 1959 (Box 11A, Folder 73)
  - Awards (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Stanford (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - AS Metals (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - A. Nuclear Soc. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - A. Phys. Soc. - Materials (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - ASEE (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - AIAA (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - AAAS (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Minutes - Stanford University Committee (Eng.), April 29, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Ann. and Forms (by Soc.), Miscellaneous (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Candidates (by name) and Forms (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Preliminary List Combined with Deadlines (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Honors and Awards Committee, Stanford Awardees List (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Text Writing (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Consulting and Professional (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - UTC Monthly Reports - HSS Consulting, 1966-67 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Capabilities of the Physical Science Laboratory, UTC Brochure 64-45, May 1964 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Chemical Laser Task Force, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Research and Development (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Mislaid Laboratory Books (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Tech Programs UTC Air Breathing (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - AIAA Business and Correspondence (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - TC Membership List (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - TAC Actions: SST Study (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Correspondence AIAA (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Final Program (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Energy Systems TC (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - IAA and IAF Business Correspondence - Letter from J. J. Harford Re: Aide Memoire on Plenary Session held during the 11th IAF Congress in Stockhold, August 1960 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - IAA Bulletins - International Academy of Astronautics Membership List, 1966 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - IAA Bulletins Beginning, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - McGraw-Hill Correspondence (Consult Ed. Contract, 1960 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Correspondence, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - McGraw-Hill Correspondence, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - McGraw-Hill: Gates-UPL, Lunar and Planetary Flight Analysis (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - IS and T Correspondence, 1966-67 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Wiley Correspondence - Dover Reprint (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Tinnan-Brown Correspondence (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Reprints AIAA-SST Study, March 1, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - JPL Publications - JPL Explorer 10th Anniversary (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Notes and Reports (non-rocket) The United States Supersonic Transport John M. Swihart, The Boeing Company (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Notes and Reprints - Amateur Rocketry (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Notes and Reports - Fluid Dynamics Theoretical Investigation of the Switching Mechanism in a Bistable..., M. Epstein (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Fluid Dynamics - Miscellaneous Articles by H. G. Heinrich (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Fluid Dynamics - The Expansion of a Rarefied Gas into a Vacuum by P. Molme, July 27, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Dynamics - Some Basic Response Relations for Reaction-Wheel Attitude Control, W. H. Cannon Jr. (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Dynamics - Basic Response Relations for Satellite Attitude Control Using Gyros, R. H. Cannon, Jr. (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Structures - Paper # 219, Introduction to Instability: A Pictorial Survey of Stability, etc., W. H. Horton, S. C. Bailey, B. H. Mcwilkin (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Clippings - John F. Kennedy Space Center (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Clippings - Space Radiators, Cooled Probes for Gas Measurement at Very High Temperatures (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Clippings - Ranger Photo Series from JPL, October 12, 1965 (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Clippings - Swingby (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - SERI File Index and Addresses (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - SERI Expenditures (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Budgets and Expenditures (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Proposal Outlines and Position Papers (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - California Siting Source Data - Fortune Survey (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Current California Research (Hoffner, Smithsonian, CSES) (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - ERDA Bulletins (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Public Information and Education (Including TV) (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Candidate Personnel (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Other Studies (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Personal Notes -HS-CTT-EQL Meeting Notes, 1971-72 (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Correspondence and Notes (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - Solar Correspondence, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - Proposals (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - Correspondence - Northrop Solar Proposal, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - Northrop Proposal (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - For Non-solar File (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - Northrop Tech. Data - Northrop Facility (Box 12, Folder 70)
  - Undergraduate Solar Program, 1975 (Box 12, Folder 71)
  - De Guerre Pool (Box 12, Folder 72)
  - Hittman Report on Domestic Energy (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - Solar UPL Reference (Box 12, Folder 74)
  - References and Sources (Box 12, Folder 75)
  - NASA-Ames Flexure Meter (solar) (Box 12, Folder 76)
  - Energy-General References (Box 12, Folder 77)
  - Solar and Peltier (SPIRES) Compendex (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Western Regional Solar Heating and Cooling Workshops and Product Exhibit (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - AIAA Technical Committee Data, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Move and Sort Logic, July 22, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - SCRA - Solar Pool Heat Plans (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Articles, Clippings and Magazines Concerning Solar Energy (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - DOD Discussion (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Mixed H2 and O2 Jets, September 7, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Irvin Benard - Hybrid Spectra (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Course Evaluation 280A (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Postoffice Research (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Vandalism Committee Beginning, April 10, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Lunar Grasshopper Publicity (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Eustis - MHD Pros. (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Vacuum Balloon (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Productive Meeting - JPL (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Electric Propulsion Notes (Piasecki) (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Teleoperators (Including AA 297 Seminar, November 15, 1972) (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Automation - JPL (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - JPL Proposals and Funding (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Courses and Advisees (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Thermoelectrics (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Correspondence and Equipment Records (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - WHP Saudi Project (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Coulombrer, Marie Farge (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Miscellaneous Papers (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - SERI Accounts (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Abeyance (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Current Projects (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - DuBra Snow Gun (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Two-Phase Flow (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Solar Energy R & D (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Amarande Ballistics, Fluid Dynamics Notes (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Tau Beta Pi Teaching Survey (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - ERDA: R & D Solicitation Requests for Research Proposals (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Hearing Requirements of Swimming Pools (Graduate Thesis) (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - SERI Proposal to ERDA (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Solar Energy Studies in Progress by Proposed SERI Member Universities, 1976-77 (Box 13A, Folder 38)
  - AIAA International Electric Propulsion Conference (Colorado State Papers) (Box 13A, Folder 39)
  - Ion Research for NASA (Colorado State) (Box 13A, Folder 40)
  - Laser-Doppler Velocimeter Lab Work (Box 13A, Folder 41)
  - Caltech Alumni Directory 1975 (Box 13A, Folder 42)
  - Caltech JPL Phone Directory 1974 (Box 13A, Folder 43)
  - Directory of Research and Scholarship at Stanford, 1975 (Box 13A, Folder 44)
  - Miscellaneous Notes, 1975-76 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Solar Brochures (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Industry Opinions on Formation of SERI (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous Solar Energy Applications, Present and Future (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous Solar Industrial, Commercial Applications (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - JPL Civil Systems (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Light Generation Dispersion Detection (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - UCLA Short Courses in Engineering and Mathematics Catalogue, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Test Report: MArtin MArietta Black Surface (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Electrical Power systems for Space (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Solar Radiation Measuring Equipment (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - National Science Foundation Guide to Programs (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - SERI Proposal - State of New Mexico (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - ERDA Solar Development Program Reports (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Berkeley Cyclotron (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - JPL Energy Program (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Berkeley Geothermal Test Facility (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Electric Power Research Institute (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Solar Applications (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - National Solar Energy Research Institute (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - SERI Proposal: California (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Slides: Solar Energy (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Personal Correspondence and Information on Solar Applications (Box 14A, Folder 23)
- Course Information Collection I
  - A. Fundamentals (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - A.1 Problems and Solutions
    - 1960 (Box 15, Folder 2-3)
    - 1961 (Box 15, Folder 4-5)
    - 1962 (Box 15, Folder 6-7-8)
    - 1963 (Box 15, Folder 9-10)
    - 1964 (Box 15, Folder 11-12)
    - 1965 (Box 15, Folder 13-14)
  - A. 2 Quizzes and Solutions
    - 1960 (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - 1961 (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - 1962 (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - 1963 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - 1964 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - 1965 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - A.3 Notes, Charts, and Data
    - Pe/Pc vs. e (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - r vs. r1 vs. alpha (gamma) neg. (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Wp vs. dv + Ws - 1 stage (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Stage Opt. Curves-Rains (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Two Cf curves (neg.) (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - Boil and Rad. H. T. Masters (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - Hybrid 1961 Data (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - Emission of CO2 and H2O (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Boil H. Tr. - 2 charts (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - A.4 Notes
    - Burr Ballistics Notes, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 30)
    - Marxman Paper - Hybrid Comb. (Box 15, Folder 31)
    - Marxman Class Notes - Hybrids (Box 15, Folder 32)
    - Wooldridge Notes - Hybrids (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - 2-Phase Flow: Crowe and Wrenn (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - HSS Notes:, October 12, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - HSS Notes:, October 9, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - HSS Notes: (solids), October 21, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Weil or McLaren - Propellants (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - A.5: Records and Schedules
    - 1960 (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - 1961 (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - 1962 (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - 1963 (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - 1964 (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - 1965 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - A.6 Source Materials
    - Reference/Source and Material (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - The Book; Miscellaneous Performance Calculations and Figures (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - B.1 Problems and Solutions
    - Problems - 1961 (NSF), 1963, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 47)
    - Problems and Solutions, 1962, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - B.2 Quizzes
    - Quizzes, 1961, 1962, 1963 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - Quizzes, 1964, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - B.3 Notes
    - Class Notes, 1964, 1965 (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - Speaker and Lecturer Notes (Box 15, Folder 52)
    - Lecturer Notes: Aaron Rose, Solid, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 53)
    - Lecturer Notes: Goalwin, Liquid, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - Speaker and Lecturer Notes: Ordahl, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 55)
    - Speaker and Lecturer Notes: Rains, 1962 (Box 15, Folder 56)
    - Lecturer Notes: Osborn, 1965 set (Box 15, Folder 57)
    - Lecturer Notes: Rains, 1964 set (Box 15, Folder 58)
    - Speaker and Lecturer Notes (Box 15, Folder 59)
    - Lecturer Notes: Ordahl, on Propellants, January 31 to February 14, 1964 (Box 15, Folder 60)
    - Lecturer Notes: Vogel, Mechanical Design, January 24, 1961 (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - B.4 Records and Schedules
    - 1962 and 1963 Records and Schedules (Box 15, Folder 62)
    - Schedules and Records, 1964-65 (Box 15, Folder 63)
  - B.5 Reference/Source and Material (Box 15A, Folder 64)
  - C.1 Problems and Solutions (Box 15A, Folder 65-73)
  - C.2 Quizzes and Solutions (Box 15A, Folder 74-75)
  - C.3 Notes
    - Speaker/Lecturer Notes - Osborn, Ordahl, Vogel (Box 15A, Folder 76)
    - Speaker Notes: Set of Vogel Notes (Box 15A, Folder 77)
  - C.4
    - Rocket Propulsion, 1961 (Box 15A, Folder 78)
    - Rocket Propulsion, 1962 (Box 15A, Folder 79)
  - C.5 Reference/Source and Material (Box 15A, Folder 80)
  - D. Electric Rockets (Box 15A, Folder 81-99)
  - D.1 Problems and Solutions (Box 15A, Folder 100-118)
  - D.2 Quizzes and Solutions, (Elec. Prop.), 1963 (Box 16, Folder 1-4)
  - D.3 Charts and Text (Box 16, Folder 5-14)
  - D.4 Notes
    - Lecturer Notes - J. E. Ohlson, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Lecturer Notes -, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Lecturer Notes - (Electrical and Nuclear Class Notes), 1962 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Lecturer Notes - Electrical Propulsion (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Lecturer Notes (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - D.5 Records and Schedules
    - Class Grades and Schedules -, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 20-21)
    - Class Grades and Schedules -, 1965 (Box 16, Folder 22-24)
  - D.6 References and Sources
    - Rocket Propulsion -, 1961 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Plasma Characteristics of the Electron... Engine (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Electrothermal, Ion, Magnetohydrodynamic Propulsion System (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - German Arcjet Work -, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - French Ion Engine Work -, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - French Ion System Study -, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - High Specific Impulse Thermo-ionic Acceleration (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - JPL Technical Report: Plasma non-Uniform and Grid Erosion in an Electron Bombardment Ion Engine (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - E. Nuclear Rocket Propulsion Course
    - Nuclear Rockets and Fundamentals (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - E.1 Nuclear Rockets: Problems (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - E.2 Nuclear Rockets: Quizzes (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - E.3 Nuclear Rockets: Charts and Text (Box 16, Folder 36-39)
  - E.4 Notes
    - Nuclear Rockets: Speaker/Lecturer Note (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Charts and Text: Yasui Notes, 1964 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Electric Propulsion Student Notes: Magnetohydrodynamics, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Speakers/Lecturers: Nuclear Propulsion (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Nuclear Rocket Propulsion: Bussard and DeLauer (Text) (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - E.5 Nuclear Rocket Technology Course
    - Course Outline (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Class Schedules (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Class Schedules (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Grades: Yasui (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - E.6 References
    - Course Reference: Fundamental Materials in Heat Exchange (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - Miscellaneous Reference Information (Box 16, Folder 50)
- Course Information Collection II
  - C.6 Chemical Rocket Design and Technology Course
    - A Preliminary Design Method for Turbopumps (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - Propellant Feed Systems for Liquid Rocket Engines (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - SPS Engine Apollo Contractor Technical Review Meeting (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - AIAA Second Propulsion Joint Specialist Conference (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - Papers: Ignition Systems, Solid Propellant Rocket Motors (Box 16, Folder 55)
    - NASA Technical Reports: Liquid Propellant Rocket Engines (Box 16, Folder 56)
    - Vogel Data: Desired Propellant Properties (Box 16, Folder 57)
    - Star Charge Nomographs (Box 16, Folder 58)
    - J. Priapi: Ignition Systems (Box 16, Folder 59)
    - Reference and Source Material (Box 16, Folder 60)
    - JPL Memo (Box 16A, Folder 61)
    - Reference and Source Material (Box 16A, Folder 62)
    - Table: High Melting Temperature Materials (Box 16A, Folder 63)
    - Simkin-UCLA-Solid Propellants (Box 16A, Folder 64)
  - D. Electric Propulsion Course
    - Course Information (Box 16A, Folder 65)
    - Take-home Final Exam (Box 16A, Folder 66)
    - Problems -, Fall 1966 (Box 16A, Folder 67)
    - Solutions -, Fall 1966 (Box 16A, Folder 68)
    - Mid-Term Quiz (Box 16A, Folder 69)
    - Final Exam -, Fall 1968 (Box 16A, Folder 70)
    - Graph Charts (Box 16A, Folder 71)
    - Tables - Ion Propulsion, Seperately Powered Rockets (Box 16A, Folder 72)
    - Speaker-Lecturer Notes: Colloids (Kesserling, 1966) (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Speaker-Lecturer Notes: Electron Bombardment Ion Engines (H. T. Johnson, 1966) (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Speaker Notes: References, (1968) (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Class Grades and Schedule -, Fall 1968 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Grades and Schedules -, Fall 1966 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Stanford Propulsion Courses -, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Solar Electric Propulsion: JPL Report (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Reference and Source Material
      - SPET: Solid Propellant Electric Thruster (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - Ion Propulsion (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - Thermoelectrostatic Generator (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - Engine Photos (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - Thermal Radiators (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Power Sources for Electric Propulsion (Box 17, Folder 13)
      - Electrostatic Propulsion (Box 17, Folder 14)
      - Summer Program Rocket Propulsion Lectures, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 15)
      - Engineering Problems of Power Sources; Thrusters for Low Acceleration Nuclear Electric Rocket (Box 17, Folder 16)
      - Air Force Report: Prototype Cesium Bombardment System (Box 17, Folder 17)
      - NASA Publications on Electric Propulsion (Box 17, Folder 18)
      - Tadpole Satellite (Box 17, Folder 19)
      - Sert Delta Spacecraft Study (Box 17, Folder 20)
      - Exploratory Electromagnetic Thruster Research (Box 17, Folder 21)
      - Computer Program for Analyzing E. P. Missions (Box 17, Folder 22)
      - Composite Ion Accelerator Grids (Box 17, Folder 23)
      - Common Solar-Electric Upper Stage for High-Energy Unmanned Missions (Box 17, Folder 24)
      - Status of Electrostatic Thrustors for Space Propulsion (Box 17, Folder 25)
      - Plasma Properties and Performance of Mercury Ion Thrusters (Box 17, Folder 26)
      - Miscellaneous NASA E. P. Publications (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - E. Nuclear Rockets Course
    - Rockets Using Nuclear Energy? - Tsien (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Heat Transfer Characteristics of Cryogenic Hydrogen at High Fluxes and Pressures- Aerojet Corporation (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Nuclear Rocket Nozzle Thermal Design Analysis - Aerojet Corporation (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Fusion Rocket Propulsion (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Research Proposal to Project SQUID (Purdue University): Properties of Particles in Two-Phase Flow Using a Laser-Doppler Technique (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Nuclear Propulsion Class Schedule and Notes:, Fall 1969 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Quizzes and Handouts (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - NERVA Program - Nuclear Rocket Nozzles (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Reprints of Lectures - Nuclear Rocket Engine Components, Fall 1966 - (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Notes for Guest Instructor Charles Rice, Nuclear Rocket Engines (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Guest Lecturer Notes (T. J. Connoly), Fall 1967 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Miscellaneous
    - Notes from 1947 Ohlienger Class, Nuclear Power Engineering (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - NERVA Photographs - Nevada Test Site (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence Regarding United Technology Corporation Publications (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Miscellaneous Clippings Regarding Rocket Propulsion (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Company Report
    - Recent Advances in Ablation (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Correspondence and Articles Regarding Rocket Nozzle Technology; Paper: Mechanisms of Thermochemical Erosion, (April 1966) (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Visiting Lecturer Notes
    - J. P. Layton, Princeton University: Propulsion Technology for Manned Planetary Missions, 1967 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - D. A. Rains, United Technology Corporation: Lectures on System Analysis, 1961 (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - D. A. Rains: Rocket Vehicle Performance (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - D. A. Rains: Liquid Propellant Rocket Motor Configuration (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - D. A. Rains: Liquid Propellants (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - D. A. Rains: Rocket Propellant Performance Calculations (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - D. A. Rains: Liquid Propellant Combinations (Box 17, Folder 51)
    - D. A. Rains: Injector Design (Box 17, Folder 52)
    - D. A. Rains: Nozzle Configurations (Box 17, Folder 53)
    - D. A. Rains: Thrust Chamber Design and Construction (Box 17, Folder 54)
    - D. A. Rains: Regeneratively-Cooled Thrust Chamber Design (Box 17, Folder 55)
    - D. A. Rains: Turbopump Design (Box 17, Folder 56)
    - D. A. Rains: Tank Pressurization System Design (Box 17, Folder 57)
    - D. A. Rains: Miscellaneous Features of Liquid Rocket Systems (Box 17, Folder 58)
    - D. A. Rains: Vehicle System Comparisons of Various Liquid Rocket Configurations (Box 17, Folder 59)
    - D. A. Rains: Rocket Engine Control (Box 17, Folder 60)
    - D. A. Rains: Vehicle Stability and Control and Engine Starting (Box 17, Folder 61)
    - D. A. Rains: Combustion Instability (Box 17, Folder 62)
    - D. A. Rains: Rocket Engine Testing (Box 17, Folder 63)
    - D. A. Rains: Liquid Rocket Engine Development (Box 17, Folder 64)
    - C. E. Woolridge, United Technology Corporation: The Hybrid Combustion Mechanism (Box 17, Folder 65)
- General Files, Part 2
  - UCLA Short Course, Electro-Thermal Propulsion: Part One of Plasma Propulsion Systems (R. D. Buhler, Electro-Optical Systems, Inc.), 1965: (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - UCLA Short Course, Electro-Thermal Propulsion (R. D. Buhler), 1962: (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Current Status and Prospects of Electrothermal Propulsion (R. J. Page, Plasmadyne Corporation, 1962) (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - AIAA Short Lecture Series: Electric Propulsion (E. L. Katz, Electro-Optical Systems, Inc., 1965) (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Survey of Electrically Powered Rockets (H. S. Seifert, 1963) (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Ion Rocket Systems (G. R. Brewer, Hughes Research Labs, 1966) (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Papers Presented at AIAA National Meetings: (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Electric Propulsion in 1964 - A Status Review (E. Stuhlinger, NASA
    - A 100-KV, 10-W Heavy Particle Thrustor (E. Cohen, C. J. Somol, D. A. Gordon, TRW Space Technology Labs, 1965)
    - A Review of the Role of Electric Propulsion (J. Lazar, J. P. Mullin, NASA, 1966)
  - Advances in Space Propulsion: Magnetohydrodynamic Propulsion (R. W. Ziemer, Electro-Optical Systems, Inc., 1962) (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - NASA Technical Report: Hollow Cathode Restartable 15 Cm. Ion Thruster, (1973) (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - AA 100: Introduction to Aeronautics and Astronautics
    - Quizzes and Solutions, 1973-74 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Solutions to Problems (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Handouts on Rocket Propulsion and Dynamics (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Handouts on Fluid and Aerodynamics, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Handouts Calculations of the Lifting Force and The Mechanics of Flight, (1966): (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Class Grades, Fall 1973, Fall 1974, Fall 1975; AA 100 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Lecture Schedules, Fall 1973, Fall 1974; AA 100 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Miscellaneous Articles on Fluid Mechanics (Box 18, Folder 17)